Contact

3215143821 (Mobile) kristyrn@rocketmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kristysheppard-msn-rn-ccrn-7b913248 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Inpatient Telemetry

Certifications

PALS

Critical Care Registered Nurse ACLS

BLS

Kristy Sheppard, MSN, RN, **CCRN**

Director of Emergency Services and Observation Medicine at AdventHealth East Orlando

Orlando, Florida

Summary

Strong healthcare services professional holding a Master of Science in Nursing with a focus on Leadership and Management. Experienced Director of Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital and health care setting. Highly skilled in nursing leadership, with a focus on operations, budgets, productivity, clinical outcomes, patient experience and team engagement.

Experience

AdventHealth

1 year 7 months

Director of Emergency Services and Observation Medicine August 2019 - Present (11 months)

East Orlando

Nurse Manager, Waterford Lakes Emergency Department December 2018 - August 2019 (9 months)

Florida Hospital

5 years 8 months

Director Of Nursing, Florida Hospital Kissimmee August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Kissimmee

Director Of Emergency Services, Waterford Lakes November 2016 - August 2017 (10 months)

Waterford Lakes

Nurse Manager Clinical Decision Unit and Pediatrics May 2015 - November 2016 (1 year 7 months)

Orlando, Florida

Assistant Nurse Manager Emergency Department November 2014 - June 2015 (8 months)

Orlando, Florida

Health First

4 years 4 months

Nurse Manager Critical Care Services January 2014 - August 2014 (8 months)

Cocoa Beach, Florida

Nurse Manager, Critical Care and Surgical Services January 2013 - January 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Nursing Administrative Supervisor January 2011 - January 2013 (2 years 1 month) Health First - Cape Canaveral Hospital

Staff Nurse ICU May 2010 - May 2011 (1 year 1 month) ICU

Robert E. Barden, M.D.

Office Manager

August 2009 - August 2012 (3 years 1 month)

Wuesthoff Health Systems
Staff Nurse/Relief Charge Nurse Emergency Dept
May 2006 - August 2009 (3 years 4 months)

Health First - Cape Canaveral Hospital Staff Nurse ICU November 2004 - May 2006 (1 year 7 months)

Robert E. Barden, M.D Cardiology/Rheumatology/Infusion Nurse September 2000 - November 2004 (4 years 3 months)

Wuesthoff Health Systems
Staff Nurse/Relief Charge Nurse Telemetry Unit
March 1999 - September 2000 (1 year 7 months)

Dukes Memorial Hospital
Charge Nurse/Staff Nurse
July 1998 - February 1999 (8 months)
Staff Nurse—Medical/Surgical and ICCU

Indiana University Health Student Nurse Extern May 1997 - July 1998 (1 year 3 months)

Education

Walden University
Master of Science, Nursing · (2010 - 2012)

Indiana University Kokomo Bachelor of Science, Nursing · (1994 - 1998)